Contact

Zahurul Nagar,Bogura Sadar, Bogura +8801983332414 (Home) noushinshoha@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/md-noushin-islam-sa-ad-1159481aa (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Python (Programming Language)
Arduino
Java

Certifications

Python Data Structures

Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python)

Md. Noushin Islam Sa'ad

Assistant Director of Event Management at Robotics Club of BRAC University

Dhaka

Summary

Experienced Director Of Event Management with a demonstrated history of working in the research industry. Skilled in Python (Programming Language), Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Word, Java, and Microsoft PowerPoint. Strong operations professional with a Undergraduate focused in CSE from BRAC University.

Experience

Robotics Club of BRAC University 2 years

Assistant Director of Event Management June 2020 - August 2021 (1 year 3 months) Dhaka, Dhaka, Bangladesh

Senior Executive September 2019 - May 2020 (9 months)

BRAC University Adventure Club Senior Executive April 2019 - December 2019 (9 months)

Education

BRAC University

Undergraduate, Computer Science and Engineering (2018 - 2022)

Govt. Shah Sultan College HSC, Science · (2014 - 2016)

Karatoa Multimedia School and College SSC · (2006 - 2014)